reviews.com 2007-12-16

# Computing Reviews, the leading online review service for computing literature.

|  | Overview |   
---|---  
|   
Reviews.com is committed to safeguarding your privacy online. Please read the following policy to understand how your personal information will be treated by reviews.com. This policy may change from time to time so please check back periodically. 

This policy will let you know:   
What information is collected from you;   
What cookies are and how they are used;   
How your information is used;   
With whom your information may be shared;   
Information relating to links to third party sites;   
What choices are available to you regarding collection and use of your information, and how you can update, correct or delete your information;  
The kind of security precautions that are in place to protect the loss, misuse, or alteration of your information;  and  
What constitutes your acceptance of this Privacy Policy.

|   
|  | What Information does Reviews.com Collect from Me? |   
---|---  
| 

**  
Personally Identifiable Information**

Reviews.com will not collect any personally identifiable information about Site Visitors except when specifically and knowingly provided by such individuals. Site Visitors can opt out of providing any personally identifiable information to reviews.com while still being able to browse and review the reviews.com Web Site (the "Site"); however, in order to access certain services provided by reviews.com or to communicate with reviews.com, Site Visitors must provide certain personally identifiable information to reviews.com. Examples of personally identifiable information are: name, postal address, email address and phone number. Reviews.com collects personally identifiable information from you (i) when you register for any of the services reviews.com provides (the "reviews.com Services"), including when you set up your profile on the Site, (ii) when/if you send feedback or questions to reviews.com via email or a feedback form on the Site, and (iii) when/if you comment on a review through a reader forum.

Reviews.com requires that you keep a valid, updated name and email address on file with reviews.com in order for you to access certain parts of the reviews.com Services. In addition, Site Visitors who utilize any reviews.com Services for which reviews.com charges a fee to Site Visitors (the "Additional Features") must maintain valid, updated billing information (including, without limitation, credit card information) on file with reviews.com. 

**Non-Personally Identifiable Information**

Reviews.com collects non-personally identifiable information (information which is not connected by reviews.com to a specific individual) from you through cookies (as further described below) and through your browser. Examples of such non-personally identifiable information include the type and version of the browser (e.g., Netscape) and the type of operating system (e.g., Windows 95 or Mac OS) you use.  

|   
|  | What are Cookies and how does Reviews.com use them? |   
---|---  
| 

Reviews.com uses a feature of your internet Web browser called a "cookie" to assign a unique identification to your computer. Cookies are files that your Web browser places on your computer's hard drive. Reviews.com creates and then uses these cookie files to track your clicks as you go through the Site.

Reviews.com may use cookies to tell us whether you have visited the Site previously, and to help us determine whether you came to the Site from a particular internet link or banner advertisement. 

Cookies may also be used to help to save and retrieve passwords used on the Site and information on certain preferences, saving you from having to re-enter this information upon every visit to the Site. Reviews.com does not and cannot use cookies to retrieve personal information about you from your computer unless such information was previously knowingly and willingly provided by you. 

You can set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie, which provides you with the opportunity to decide whether you want to accept or reject the cookie. Please continue to review this Privacy Policy so that you are aware of our current policy with respect to cookies.    

|   
|  | How does Reviews.com use my information? |   
---|---  
|   
Reviews.com uses the information we collect from Site Visitors to help target information dissemination about reviews.com, to help us to determine what new features to develop on the Site, and to help us determine the popularity and effectiveness of various Site features. Reviews.com also uses such information to send information requested by Site Visitors to such Site Visitors, to periodically notify Site Visitors of new and/or existing features, to tell Site Visitors about promotions and service availability, to provide Site Visitors with other notifications, to improve the Web Site Visitor experience with reviews.com and to better manage and maintain the reviews.com Services. However, you should know that reviews.com will only send communications to Site Visitors if such Site Visitors have "opted in" to receive or requested such communications. Information may be used on an individual basis or in the aggregate.  
|   
|  | With Whom does Reviews.com share my information? |   
---|---  
| 

Reviews.com respects your privacy. Reviews.com does not share, sell, rent, or loan any personally identifiable information regarding any Site Visitor to or with any third party, except for the Association for Computing Machinery, Inc. ("ACM"). By accepting this Privacy Policy, you consent to the sharing of your personally identifiable information with ACM. [ACM will not share or use your personally identifiable information, other than to provide you with copies of articles you request, to review and analyze recommendations you provide to reviews.com regarding articles or reviewers, and to contact you if you submit a review to reviews.com that ACM wishes to use or publish].

Reviews.com may share aggregated, non-personally identifiable information with third parties. This information will not be linked to any personally identifiable information. 

Notwithstanding the foregoing, reviews.com may comply with any subpoena, order of court, or request by a regulatory or law enforcement agency to gain access to any of the information, including without limitation personally identifiable information, which reviews.com collects.   

|   
|  | What About Links to Third Party Sites? |   
---|---  
|   
The Site may be linked to other sites that are not under the control of or maintained by reviews.com. Please be aware that reviews.com is providing these links to you only as a convenience, and that the privacy policies of such sites may be different from this Privacy Policy. Reviews.com is not responsible for the privacy policies of other sites. Please be sure to read the privacy policies of other sites you visit after linking from this Site.  
|   
|  | What Are My Choices Regarding Use Of Information, And How Can I Update, Correct or Delete Any Information? |   
---|---  
|   
As described above, reviews.com may, from time to time, send you certain communications. If you do not want to receive such communications, at any time you can edit your reviews.com account information and tell us to no longer send such communications to you by clicking on this link. In addition, if you would like to update, change or delete any of your account information, you may do so by clicking on this link and then following the instructions provided.  
|   
|  | What Security Precautions Are In Place To Protect The Loss, Misuse, Or Alteration Of My Information? |   
---|---  
| 

Your account information is password-protected so that you and only you have access to this personally identifiable information. We recommend that you do not divulge your password to anyone. Also, remember to sign out of your reviews.com account and close your browser window when you have finished accessing the Site. This is to ensure that others cannot access your personally identifiable information if you share a computer with someone else or are using a computer in a public place.

Reviews.com takes steps to ensure that your personally identifiable information is treated securely and in accordance with this Privacy Policy. In addition to password protecting your account information, reviews.com will encrypt any credit card information that reviews.com collects using SSL (Secure Socket Layer). 

Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while reviews.com strives to protect your personal information, reviews.com cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us via email, through the Site, or through the reviews.com Services, and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission, we make our best effort to ensure its security on our systems.   

|   
|  | What Constitutes My Acceptance Of This Privacy Policy? |   
---|---  
| 

**BY USING THE REVIEWS.COM SERVICES AND/OR THE SITE, YOU EXPRESSLY CONSENT TO THE USE AND DISCLOSURE OF YOUR INFORMATION, BOTH PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE AND NON-PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE, AS DESCRIBED IN THIS PRIVACY POLICY.**

Reviews.com reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time by electronic notice posted on the Site. Your continued use of the Site after the date that such notices are posted will be deemed to be your agreement to the changed terms. 

**Additional Information  
**Questions regarding this statement should be directed to [privacypolicy@reviews.com](mailto:privacypolicy@reviews.com).

|
